Marvelous Designer is a 3D cloth simulation software and it lets you create digital
clothing just like the real-life garments. Instead of creating it by sculpting from
the solid objects, you can easily just create patterns and cut them and sew them together,
and you can see them move in real life. The Seagroup Asia experience so far,
it's really really fascinating. We were able to get to meet a lot of personal users,
student users, and also the enterprise ones. They're not only working on the clothes,
they're also working on a lot of the environmental assets, and I think that really motivates us to
like expand more to enter into different industries.
The software, MD, has saved me a lot of time. I've been able to create some real-life
clothes, and at the same time, it's very fast. In the end, I hope that in the future,
MD will be able to bring out more features.